<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Robert Huang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:3503/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Robert Huang</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:3503/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Coaching Carousel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2024/06/26/the-coaching-carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2024/06/26/the-coaching-carousel/</guid>
      <description>Being a head coach or manager of a sports team must be among the world’s most unstable professions given the number of teams that go through coaching changes in a season. Whether it’s an impatient front office, angry fanbase, or ambitious coach chasing a better situation, a lot of turnover is expected in this line of work. We’ll look at exactly how volatile this job is by analyzing some of America’s most popular sports leagues — the NFL, NBA, MLB, NHL, and WNBA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formula One Grand Prix Start Times</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2022/05/13/formula-one-grand-prix-start-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2022/05/13/formula-one-grand-prix-start-times/</guid>
      <description>Formula One is an international racing series with Grand Prix held across the globe. The race calendar has expanded and moved around throughout the years, with a previously European-heavy lineup now being supplemented with more Middle Eastern/Asian and American events. Races generally start off in the afternoon, but there are locations that now feature night races. How many races fans get to easily experience live depends on where they live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Playoffs - Best Players to Have Never Advanced</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2020/06/13/nba-playoffs-best-players-to-have-never-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2020/06/13/nba-playoffs-best-players-to-have-never-advanced/</guid>
      <description>There is no greater measure of success in the NBA than performance in the playoffs. For the biggest names in the sport, whether their resumes include an NBA championship is sometimes a referendum on their careers. Michael Jordan and Bill Russell finish atop many greatest players of all-time lists because of their postseason achievements. Conversely, guys like Karl Malone and Charles Barkley are knocked down some rankings because they never won a ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Hometowns</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2020/04/27/nba-hometowns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2020/04/27/nba-hometowns/</guid>
      <description>Background NBA players come from all across the United States, but some areas of the country have greater reputations as centers of basketball activity than others. Which American cities have produced the most NBA players and has this changed throughout the NBA’s history? Are basketball hotbeds from the 1960s still producing the same number of players today or has the game shifted geographically? We will try to answer these questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gender Age Gap in Hollywood Romances</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2019/12/24/the-gender-age-gap-in-hollywood-romances/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2019/12/24/the-gender-age-gap-in-hollywood-romances/</guid>
      <description>Humphrey Bogart and Audrey Hepburn in Sabrina (1954), Cary Grant and Grace Kelly in To Catch a Thief (1955), and more recently, Daniel Day Lewis and Vicky Krieps in Phantom Thread (2017). What is immediately noticeable when watching those films (at least for this viewer) is the huge age difference between the male leads and their on-screen romantic partners. Humphrey Bogart is nearly 30 years older than Audrey Hepburn. Cary Grant and Daniel Day Lewis are each about 25 years older than Grace Kelly and Vicky Krieps, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Draft vs. Draft Boards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2019/08/13/nba-draft-vs-draft-boards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2019/08/13/nba-draft-vs-draft-boards/</guid>
      <description>Background Heading into the NBA draft, the is a general consensus on the rough order that the current crop of prospects should be selected. This can be seen through the numerous draft boards for a given year available on many websites, created by both professional and amateur draft prognosticators. Analysts project who they think will have the best NBA careers using a combination of their own scouting abilities, some group think, and, for the more well-connected individuals, whatever information they may have gathered from league insiders or team executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Gold 101 Restaurants - Mapped</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2019/06/12/jonathan-gold-101-restaurants-mapped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2019/06/12/jonathan-gold-101-restaurants-mapped/</guid>
      <description>Background The late Jonathan Gold, former Pulitzer Prize winning food critic for the Los Angeles Times and before that, LA Weekly, released an annual list of the city’s best restaurants between 2005 and 2017. These restaurants spanned Los Angeles and Orange County and included all types of cuisines and price points. Despite the yearly lists being the work of a single critic, they provided a sense of the pulse of the Los Angeles dining scene for each of those years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Awards Voting - Outlier Ballots Using PCA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2018/12/10/nba-awards-voting-outlier-ballots-using-pca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2018/12/10/nba-awards-voting-outlier-ballots-using-pca/</guid>
      <description>Background We follow up the previous post on NBA awards voting with a closer look at the Most Valuable Player (MVP) award. MVP is voted on by a panel of about 100 to 130 media members (a different group depending on the year) after the end of the regular NBA season. Voters rank 5 players on their ballots in preferential order with 1st place receiving 10 points, 2nd place 7 points, 3rd place 5 points, 4th place 3 points, and 5th place 1 point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Awards Voting - Hometown Bias</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2018/11/13/nba-awards-voting-hometown-bias/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2018/11/13/nba-awards-voting-hometown-bias/</guid>
      <description>Background The end of season awards for the NBA are voted upon by a panel of media members that include national writers, national broadcasters/announcers, studio analysts, and team beat writers. Up until the 2016-17 season, this group also included team employed broadcasters. NBA fans who have spent enough time watching games on League Pass may have noticed why this was an issue, with hometown biases among many local announcers evident during the call of games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Draft - Best/Worst Picks by Team and General Manager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/post/2018/10/10/nba-draft-best-worst-picks-by-team-and-general-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/post/2018/10/10/nba-draft-best-worst-picks-by-team-and-general-manager/</guid>
      <description>Background In recent years, the Sacramento Kings used top 10 draft picks on Thomas Robinson, Ben McLemore, and Jimmer Freddette (I would have included Georgios Papagiannis, but he went 13th). The San Antonio Spurs, on the other hand, were able to get Kawhi Leonard at 15, Tony Parker at 28, and Manu Ginobili at 57. Is all of this luck or are there certain teams or front offices that are more skilled at drafting than others?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3503/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:3503/about/</guid>
      <description>This site will feature projects and analyses that I work on for fun in my free time. Hopefully, some of you will find some entertainment from my musings. I also watch a lot of movies, but not at the rate I used to.&#xA;Contact me at robrt.huang@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
