<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nba Draft on Robert Huang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:6269/tags/nba-draft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nba Draft on Robert Huang</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:6269/tags/nba-draft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NBA Draft vs. Draft Boards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:6269/post/2019/08/13/nba-draft-vs-draft-boards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:6269/post/2019/08/13/nba-draft-vs-draft-boards/</guid>
      <description>Background Heading into the NBA draft, the is a general consensus on the rough order that the current crop of prospects should be selected. This can be seen through the numerous draft boards for a given year available on many websites, created by both professional and amateur draft prognosticators. Analysts project who they think will have the best NBA careers using a combination of their own scouting abilities, some group think, and, for the more well-connected individuals, whatever information they may have gathered from league insiders or team executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Draft - Best/Worst Picks by Team and General Manager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:6269/post/2018/10/10/nba-draft-best-worst-picks-by-team-and-general-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:6269/post/2018/10/10/nba-draft-best-worst-picks-by-team-and-general-manager/</guid>
      <description>Background In recent years, the Sacramento Kings used top 10 draft picks on Thomas Robinson, Ben McLemore, and Jimmer Freddette (I would have included Georgios Papagiannis, but he went 13th). The San Antonio Spurs, on the other hand, were able to get Kawhi Leonard at 15, Tony Parker at 28, and Manu Ginobili at 57. Is all of this luck or are there certain teams or front offices that are more skilled at drafting than others?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
